JAY TAVITAS

ART DIRECTOR

jaytavitas81@gmail.com 210.279.5859 San Antonio, TX behance.net/jtavitas

Art director with over 18 years experience in developing creative for numerous marketing and advertising campaigns. Currently working on a certificate in UX/UI from the University of Texas, San Antonio with skills in Adobe Creative Suite, video editing, script writing, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Visual Prototyping & Wireframing. Art direction background coupled with research skills and an eye for modern design principles, makes me a valuable addition to any team.

EXPERIENCE

- · Conceptualizing, designing, and presenting marketing creative and campaigns
- Providing art and creative direction
- Leading and mentoring creative teams
- Collaborating with lines of businesses, management, and executives
- Organizing and managing multiple design projects on time and on budget
- Developing and maintaining working relationships with various vendors and advertising agencies
- Planning and art directing photo shoots
- · Interviewing users, developing persona profiles and mapping the user's journey
- Adapting prototypes based on usability feedback

WORK HISTORY

ART DIRECTOR

Visionworks of America 2016 - Currently

GRAPHICS COORDINATOR

Archdiocese of San Antonio 2016 - 2016

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Security Service Federal Credit Union 2010 - 2016

SENIOR GRAPHIC DESIGNER

H-E-B Grocery Co. 2007 - 2010

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

NuPrints 2004 - 2007

SKILLS

- Adobe Creative Cloud
- Conceptual Design
- Print and Web Design
- UX/UI
- Animation
- Script Writing
- Art Direction
- Creative Direction
- Strategic Thinker
- Time Management
- Good Communication Skills
- Strong Work Ethic
- Quick Learner
- Problem Solver

EDUCATION

GRAPHIC DESIGN

San Antonio College 2002-2003

COMPUTER SCIENCE

St. Mary's University 1999-2001